[{"answer": "I love Fergie, it's a great name.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Now, what have I done?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Did you really do it?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "She came to Wall Street and she sang for the Sarah Ferguson Foundation.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Did she really?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "Well, I actually was thinking before I came on this show that actually Sarah is the same sitting here as she was then, she just made a few road changes and changed course a few times.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "What was Sarah like before the royal experience began?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "That's when you first met him?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Yes, very well.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "And do you remember that moment?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I think the word \"dating\" is kind of interesting because when you go -- when you date a prince back in those long years ago, 26 years ago, it's not -- you can't actually go on a date.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "When you first started actually dating him, did you have any comprehension of what you were getting yourself into?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "As fast as that.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "As fast as that?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Let me go back in time.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "What was that moment like?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "He had a much better idea than I did, I think.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Do you think he knew what you were going to be immersed in?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, you know what's so great is they have got a great role model of mistakes to follow.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Do you think they've learned from what they saw you go through, how to play negative media perhaps a little better than you were able to because they saw the way to do it well and the way maybe not to do it so well?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "I think it's more of a -- it's a cultural thing.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Oh, isn't it?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, I think that I believed the good press for the two years before then -- so, I was believing my own press, which is the most dangerous thing you can do, isn't it, because now I know.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "But that experience, when it turned, what was that like for you?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "The thing about Andrew is that really our love is so strong.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "When there was a point of no return, did you think?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "Well, I think that -- as I said, we're a very modern fairy tale.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "I mean, is it completely unthinkable that one day the two of you could actually get back together?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Every minute of my day, I have to work on regret now, Piers, every day, because I regret divorcing and I regret that I wasn't more aware.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "What are your biggest regrets, as the marriage fell apart and the press dived in, and all these exposes about you and your life, what for you personally were the things you most regret now doing in that period?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I think --", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Do you feel ashamed of your behavior in that period?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "I think looking back -- of course, with having worked with Dr. Phil and Suze Orman and Martha Beck and Oprah, looking back -- goodness, with the awareness I have now, yes, I feel so totally ashamed.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Or do you feel it was kind of a consequence of all the attacks on you?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Well, I remember seeing it and just going, \"Oh, no, Sarah.\"", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "When you saw that front page, what went through your mind?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "And that's when Carolyn, my best friend in the world -- do you remember Carolyn?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, like he always reacts when anything is written or anything is said about me or the girls, complete solidarity to his family.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "How did Andrew react when he saw that?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well, I think like anybody who divorces a family member, it's -- you know, you mustn't ever expect to be invited.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Of all the royals over the years, who have been the most supportive to you?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I was in Thailand at a place called Kamilayah (ph).", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "How did you feel that day watching it all?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Your girls were great that day.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "So it's pretty good here, isn't' it?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Yes, very dear.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "That charity is very dear to your heart, isn't it?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Well, before she got married, I called her Dutch, because she was born for it, you know, born to be a princess.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "What was she like, Diana?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "She was hilarious.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Do you remember her wit?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Well, we don't really know.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "What was that about?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "I was in Italy.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Where were you when you heard that she died?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "ERGUSON: Honestly, total pride, total pride.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "How would she have felt on the royal wedding day, do you think, watching her boy, William going down the aisle?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I think they -- I don't know except they would have been the best friends.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Be honest here, knowing her well, what do you think she would have made of Kate?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I take my hat off to her.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Pretty impressive Kate, isn't she?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I think she's able to cope with it.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Do you worry about the pressure that you know she's going to be facing?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Totally.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "I think so, don't you think?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "I think my friend who helped me with the charity, Johnny -- I think Johnny has never really got over it, because he just couldn't believe it, because that was his world, you know.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "When you realized that -- what was happening to the people in there and you realized how close you came to being one of them, what was going through your mind?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "I think it's going to be amazing.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "When William and Kate go to Hollywood, it's going to be pretty crazy, isn't it?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "You didn't remember it very often, did you?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "I always say when you've had the best, forget the rest, you know.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "Would you like to find a new Mr. Right in your life?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110609pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "We can do CNN dateline?", "qSentId": 686}]